{
    "id": "74e158af2ea94a449db5335f36f0bcc5",
    "title": "Much and Many Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. are called but few are chosen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dee817f40c7f44ec8ddb9cc765c99de4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have told you ……………. times that I do not like horror movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7955b0d6eb6d4a06aa0ea627412e088a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She does not have ……………. friends in town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afb70d39d2034f73a958b010c85e28ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "The writer is ……………… revered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e5a0ae2e1624c6184362c75dd34bec6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you go there ……………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b3debe13937949719051df564b3de761"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ……………. money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0963cfe870084f3183236ce148ea6656"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got ……………. work ahead of us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "147acaa011144f5e91c1c2788add604c"
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of the hype, the film is not ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2545666e9b52401eac5bfb102b502b97"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has acted in …………… Kannada movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efc77d6dcb17487389e342aa1a0a0097"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………. of the roof needs repairing?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "782e818cb91047b0941667532d62fa10"
        }
    ]
}